Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Architectural Records, 1912-1982 and undated (Box 119)
  - Modifications for 556-A PBX Framework for Use As a 740-BE PBX. Western Electric Company. 1956 Mar 27. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Line Relay Unit with or without Key-Lite Operation 2 x 23 Inch Mounting Plate Surface Wired. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 1. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Frame Equipment. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Frame Equipment. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Frame Equipment. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Frame Equipment. Western Electric Company. 1959 Jun 12. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specifications for Writing Shelf Assembly. Western Electric Company. 1960 Jun 7. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector or Inter-Frame Connector. Western Electric Company. 1960 Apr 25. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector or Inter-Frame Connector. Western Electric Company. 1961 Apr 25. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Assembly, Wiring and Equipment for Hunting Selector-Connector or Inter-Frame Connector. Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 4. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Switchboard Section. Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 13. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Cable Forms and Connecting Tables for 1st Switch Frame Used with 100 Line Manual Switchboard (Dwg 1). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 30. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Cable Forms and Connecting Tables for 1st Switch Frame Used with 100 Line Manual Switchboard (Dwg 2). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 30. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Cable Forms and Connecting Tables for 1st Switch Frame Used with 100 Line Manual Switchboard (Dwg 3). Western Electric Company. 1961 Oct 30. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Switchboard Section (Dwg 2). Western Electric Company. [1961 Oct 13]. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - Specification for Switchboard Section (Dwg 3). Western Electric Company. [1961 Oct 13]. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F5, Box 119)
  - 100 Point Line Finder. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1949 Jan 17. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Cord, Telephone, Dial, Battery, Buzzer and Ringing Circuits. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1949 Jan 17. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1958 Dec 9. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Alarm Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Central Office Trunk Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - 100 Point Line Finder. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Equipment Ordering Drawing. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1960 Jan 5. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Wiring List and Installation Information. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment (Dwg 1). Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment (Dwg 2). Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment (Dwg 3). Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment (Dwg 4). Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Specification for 50 or 100 Line Manual or Key-Lite Frame Equipment (Dwg 6). Western Electric Company. 1961 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F6, Box 119)
  - Traffic Register Mounting Plate for #14 Type. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1956 Jun 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Jack Circuit, Universal for Combination Trunks or Tie Trunk. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1956 Aug 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Miscellaneous Circuits. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1960 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Wiring List and Installation Information. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Modification of 556 Switchboard. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Station Line Circuit T 65661 12 & T 532565 Mod. For Interframe Connections Circuits 54 to 58 Only. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Cabling for H-919-215 Switchframes, Ampherol Connector Cables. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1963 Jan 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Drawing Lists, H-919-215 Frame Equipment. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company.1963 Jan 9. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Cabling Arrangement, H-919-270 Frame or Mod. H-919-215 Frame. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1963 Dec 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Telephone Unit, D3 Wiring. Western Electric Company. 1956 Nov 21. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Central Office Trunk Unit, 2 x 23 Inch Mounting Plate, Surface Wired. Western Electric Company. 1957 Aug 18. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Cord Unit, 1 Circuit D3 Wiring. Western Electric Company. 1960 Aug 6. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Cord Unit. Western Electric Company. 1960 Aug 6. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Cord Circuit Unit, One Circuit D3 Wiring. 1960 Nov 30. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Specification for Cord Circuit Unit, One Circuit D3 Wiring. 1960 Nov 30. Positive Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F7, Box 119)
  - Alarm Circuit. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. 1949 Jan 3. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Attendant Trunk Circuit from Selector or Selector Connector Levels. Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. Undated. Positive blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Reserve Power Plant for 740 BE 50 and 100 Line. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1958 May 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Power Plants, Rectifier Ringing and Tone and Switchboard Fuse Equipment for 740 BE PBX 50 or 90 Line. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1958 May 29. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Power Plants, Rectifier Ringing and Tone and Switchboard Fuse Equipment for 740 BE PBX 50 or 90 Line. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1958 Jun 3. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Modification of 556 Switchboard. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1958 Apr 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - 740 BE Equipment Ordering Drawing. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Feb 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Modification of Term. Strips, B1, B2 and B3 H-919-270 Switchframes. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Jack Circuit, Universal for Combination Trks. Tie Trks. Or Misc. Ckts. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - "A" Conn Cables for NJ-X-7250 25 Swbd. & H-919-270 Sw. Fr. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Mar 19. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Switchboard Cabling for H-919-215 Switchframes, Ampherol Connector Cables. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1963 Jan 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Modified 556A Switchboard for Use in 740 BE PBX Jack Figures. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1961 Aug 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Modified 556A Switchboard for Use in 740 BE PBX Jack Figures. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1961 Aug 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - Modified 556A Switchboard for Use in 740 BE PBX Jack Figures. New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. 1962 Apr 4. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D4F8, Box 119)
  - #48 Plastic House - Wood Frame With Center Post Covered With Weatherable Mylar. Geo. J. Ball, Inc. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - #58-30' Plastic House - Wood Frame With Clear 30 Ft. Span Covered with Weatherable Mylar. Geo. J. Ball, Inc. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - #58-24' Plastic House - Wood Frame With Clear span Covered With Weatherable Mylar. Geo. J. Ball, Inc. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - #78 Plastic House - Designed for Handipanels Glazed with Weatherable Mylar. Geo. J. Ball, Inc. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - #88 Plastic House - Wood Frame With Clear 20 Ft. Span Covered with Weatherable Mylar. Geo. J. Ball, Inc. 1962 May 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Plot Plan - New Range of Greenhouses for Mr. J. B. Duke Sommerville, NJ. William H. Lutton. 1922 Apr 14. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Range of Greenhouses for Mr. J. B. Duke Sommerville, NJ. William H. Lutton. 1922 Apr 14. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Range of Greenhouses for Mr. J. B. Duke Sommerville, NJ. William H. Lutton. 1922 Apr 14. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Ground Plan - New Range of Greenhouses for Mr. J. B. Duke Sommerville, NJ. William H. Lutton. 1922 Apr 14. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Range of Greenhouses for Mr. J. B. Duke Sommerville, NJ. William H. Lutton. 1922 Apr 14. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Cross Section Showing Gablet End [Partial]. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Plot Plan. Lord & Burnham. 1959 May 7. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - [Greenhouses for Carnations, Roses, Violets, and Hybrid]. Lord & Burnham. 1900 Jun 11. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Duke Farm Price Quote. Somerset Plumbing Supply Co. 1964 Feb 4. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Piping to Convert Existing Boiler to Steam Service. Horace M. Patrick. 1961 Jul 24. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Heating Plan. Lord & Burnham. 1959 Jan 30. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Door to Rose House. Lord & Burnham. 1905 May 11. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Weathermatic Irrigation System. Fertl-Soil Co. 1966 Sep 6. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D5F6, Box 119)
  - Proposed Gutter Extensions. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Sep 12. Diazo; photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 1 of 14 (includes 3 page letter to Anton Gsell from L. Rubel asking for approval on the drawings). Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 2 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 3 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 4 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 5 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 6 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 7 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 8 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 9 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 10 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 11 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 12 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 13 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Renovations Chinese & Desert Houses, 14 of 14. Horowitz & Wirth; IBG, Inc.; Lord & Burnham, 1975 Jun 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F2, Box 119)
  - Proposed French Garden Enclosure Scheme #1. Richard M. Horowitz. 1980 Jan 25. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Wall Sill Plan, C-1. Lord & Burnham. 1973 Dec 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi -Tropical Scale Plans, C-2. Lord & Burnham. 1973 Dec 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Colonial American Garden Scale Plans, C-3. Lord & Burnham. 1974 Jan 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Tropical & Colonial Amer. Gardens, Greenhouse Section, C-4. Lord & Burnham. 1973 Dec 23. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Tropical & Colonial Amer. Gardens, Side Details, C-5. Lord & Burnham. 1973 Dec 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Trop. & Colon. Ridge & Roof Details, C-6. Lord & Burnham. 1973 Dec 28. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Trop & Col. Amer. Gardens, Partition Details, C-7. Lord & Burnham. 1974 Jan 11. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Trop & Col. Amer. Gardens, Partition Details, C-8. Lord & Burnham. 1974 Jan 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Sill Detail at Connection of Colonial Amer. & Semi-Tropical Gardens to the Italian Garden, C-9. Lord & Burnham; Roberts, William A. 1974 Jan 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Semi-Trop. & Colon. Amer. Gardens, Side Vent Details, C-10. Lord & Burnham; Roberts, William A. 1974 Jan 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Colonial American Garden Partition Door Details, C-11. Lord & Burnham; Roberts, William A. 1974 Jan 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Planting Plan for the English Garden, C-12. Lord & Burnham; Roberts, William A. 1974 Jan 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F3, Box 119)
  - Scale Plans House #19-21, #1. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Scale Plans House #16, #2. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Scale Plans House #17 & #18, #3. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Side Detail - Transom Sash & Fixed Glaz., Houses (19-21) (16) (17-18), #4. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Conn. Dets. At North End - Hse #19-21, #5. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Dets at South End of House #19-21, #6. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Fixed Glaz. Side Details House #17-18, #7. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Dets North End of House #16, #8. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Dets - East & West End House #17-18, #9. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Gablet at North End of Hse #16, #10. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Conn. Hse. #16 to Japanese Gard., #11. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1976 Sep 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Ridge & Roof Details, Houses # (19-21) (16) (17 &18). Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1969 May 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Blue Ribbon Century 10' 3-3/4" Bays, Standard Rack & Pinion Roof Sash Operator. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1969 Jun 10. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Blue Ribbon House 10' 3-3/4" Bays, Standard Arm & Rod Side Sash Operator. Horowitz & Wirth; Innocenti & Webel; Lord & Burnham. 1969 Jun 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F4, Box 119)
  - Redwood - Inswinging Single Door Details, Blue Ribbon House Construction at Trans Partn House #5 & North End of House #8, D-1. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Wood Outswinging Single Door Details, Blue Ribbon Century Greenhouse Constr. at West End of House #2, D-2. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Alum. Inswinging Single Door Details, Blue Ribbon Century Hse Construction Side Door to Gro-mor & Annex, D-3. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Greenhouse Scale Plans Houses #1-2 & #5-6-7-8, #1A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Sill Plan & Sections, Houses #1-2 & #5-6-7-8, #2A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Side Detail - Transom Sash & Fixed Glaz. Houses #5-6-7-8 & North Side of #1 & 2, #3A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Side Dets Fixed Glazing South Side Houses #1 & 2, #4A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - House #1 Conn. To Work Room, Dr'g #7A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Ridge & Roof Details Houses #1-#2-#5-#6-#7-#8. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1969 May 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Connection Details House #8 to #2, #5A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - House #8 & Canopy Conns Hse #2, #6A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Transverse Partition Details, Blue Ribbon Century Greenhouse Plans, #8A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/D.D. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Dets of Connections to French Garden & Annex, #9A. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/D.D. 1978 Jun 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Bill of Material. Lord & Burnham/ J.V.R. 1964 May 12. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D6F5, Box 119)
  - Duke Gardens Heating Chart. Undated. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D6F7, Box 119)
  - Preliminary Site Study for Duke Gardens Foundation. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Sep 8. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F7, Box 119)
  - French Garden Planting Plan. Includes plant list. Innocenti & Webel. 1960 May 15. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - [House 23 Floor Plan]. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Jul 21. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - A Cactus Garden. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1960 Aug 16. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - English Garden. JAE. 1960 Jun 1. Diazo; pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - [Water & Electricity for English & Japanese Gardens]. Undated. Negative photostat. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - Planting Plan for the French Garden. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1959 Aug 1. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F8, Box 119)
  - Palm House Plan & Sections. Horowitz & Wirth. 1976 Feb 20. 1976. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Work R'm - Corridor Details. Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 18. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - (Work Room) - Passage Conn. To New G'h'se (North Side). Horowitz & Wirth; Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1978 May 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Proposed Planting for French Garden. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Diazo and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Bed & Walk Study. Innocenti & Webel. 1958 Nov 21. Pencil and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Hydrants in Box Garden. Innocenti & Webel. [1900] Sep 2. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Diagram for Box Garden. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - [Interior Sketch of Greenhouse 23]. Innocenti & Webel. Undated. Diazo and pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - General Construction Details. Innocenti & Webel. 1959 Jan 20. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Moorish Garden Area. Undated. Pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Proposed Extension to Range of Glass. Lord & Burnham. 1912 Mar 1. Blueprint. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Restoration South Gable of Edwardian Garden. Lord & Burnham/ D.D. 1974 Jun 14. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - General Notes & Elevations. Horowitz & Wirth. 1979 Nov 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Outline Mounting Detail. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ E.W.L. 1957 Nov 21. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Wiring Diagram. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ E.W.L. 1958 Mar 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Wiring Diagram. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ E.W.L. 1959 Apr 2. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Wiring Diagram. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc. 1959 Aug 13. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Wiring Diagram. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ C.I.P. 1959 Oct 26. Photocopy. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Wiring Diagram. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ C.I.P. 1959 Nov 17. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - A.C. Output Control W.D. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Outline - Installation. D.W. Onan & Sons, Inc./ J.W.Z. 1959 Jan 22. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F9, Box 119)
  - Planting Plan for the English Garden. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1959 Dec. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English & French Gardens, Dwg. No. 3. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1959 Dec. Diazo and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English & French G'n'h's, #4. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Feb. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English & French G'n'h's, #5. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Feb. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English Garden Wall, #6. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Mar. Diazo and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English G'n'd Paving, #7. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Mar. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English Courtyard, #9. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Mar. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - English Garden Fence, #10. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Mar. Diazo and colored pencil. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - French Garden, #11. Frederick W.G. Peck. 1960 Mar. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F10, Box 119)
  - A Spanish Garden for Duke Farms. Richard C. Tongg, architect. 1959 Aug 12. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F13, Box 119)
  - Semi Tropical Garden Partition Door Details. Mohd Amin., Senior Draftsman. Undated. Diazo. (Opaperfolder C2D6F13, Box 119)